These days there is so much tempting technology to look at: smartphones, tablets, computer games and TV screens.
如今有太多吸引人的科技产品可供关注：智能手机、平板电脑、电脑游戏和电视屏幕。
Much of our entertainment and education comes from using them, so it's no wonder we spend so much time staring at them.
我们的大部分娱乐和教育都来自于使用这些设备，所以难怪我们会花这么多时间盯着它们看。
But even if the saying that looking at a screen for too long gives you square eyes isn't true, there is still some concern that it can affect your eyesight.
不过，尽管“长时间看屏幕会让眼睛变方”的说法并不属实，人们仍担心这会影响视力。
So, should we be worried?
那么，我们应该担心吗？
Certainly for children who spend hours glued to a screen there is a concern that their health might be at risk.
对于那些连续数小时黏在屏幕前的孩子来说，他们的健康确实可能面临风险，这一点令人担忧。
The lack of physical activity can lead to an increase in their weight.
缺乏体育活动可能会导致体重增加。
But there is a fear that their eyesight is deteriorating too.
但人们也担心他们的视力会下降。
Although there's not much evidence to prove this yet, recent findings have opened our eyes to the issue.
尽管目前还没有太多证据证明这一点，但最近的研究结果让我们开始关注这个问题。
Katherine Sellgren from BBC News spoke to Chris Hammond, professor of ophthalmology at King's College London and consultant ophthalmic surgeon at St Thomas' Hospital.
英国广播公司新闻部的凯瑟琳·塞尔格伦采访了克里斯·哈蒙德教授，他是伦敦国王学院的眼科学教授，同时也是圣托马斯医院的眼科顾问医生。
He said "We know that myopia, or short-sightedness, is becoming more common…
他说：“我们知道，近视正变得越来越普遍……
It has reached epidemic levels in East Asia, Singapore, Taiwan, South Korea, where approaching 90% of 18-year-olds are now short-sighted."
在东亚、新加坡、台湾地区和韩国，近视已经达到了流行病的程度，这些地区近90%的18岁青少年现在都患有近视。”
But can this be linked to children's obsession with using electronic gadgets?
但这与孩子们沉迷使用电子设备有关吗？
Annegret Dahlmann-Noor, consultant ophthalmologist at Moorfields Eye Hospital in London says lack of natural light seems to be the key issue.
伦敦摩尔菲尔德眼科医院的眼科顾问医生安内格雷特·达尔曼-努尔表示，缺乏自然光似乎是关键问题。
She's suggested that children in East Asia study a lot, using computers, smartphones or tablets, and they are go outside less, which could be a cause of short-sightedness.
她指出，东亚的孩子学习负担重，经常使用电脑、智能手机或平板电脑，而且很少外出，这可能是导致近视的一个原因。
Wearing glasses is one solution, but it's not ideal.
戴眼镜是一种解决办法，但并不理想。
This leads to a dilemma: achieving short-term academic success or protecting your long-term eyesight.
这就导致了一个两难境地：是追求短期的学业成功，还是保护长期的视力。
It's always going to be a challenge to drag children away from their screens and it's likely that more and more studying will be done online, through a screen.
把孩子从屏幕前拉开总是一件具有挑战性的事情，而且未来越来越多的学习可能会通过屏幕在线进行。
But despite that, Professor Hammond says, "in countries like urban China, where 10% of children in each class per year are becoming short-sighted from about the age of six, there's an argument for saying we should be trying to prevent it."
不过，哈蒙德教授表示：“在类似中国这些国家的城市地区，从六岁左右开始，每个班级每年有10%的孩子会患上近视，因此我们应该努力预防这种情况。”
It's evidence we can't turn a blind eye to.
这种迹象，我们不能视而不见。
So, maybe it's time to hit the 'off' button and get our children outside?
所以，或许是时候按下“关闭”键，让孩子们到户外去了？